<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://abaksy.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://abaksy.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-02-03T07:28:31+00:00</updated><id>https://abaksy.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="https://abaksy.github.io/blog/2025/hello-world/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!"/><published>2025-01-03T12:39:16+00:00</published><updated>2025-01-03T12:39:16+00:00</updated><id>https://abaksy.github.io/blog/2025/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://abaksy.github.io/blog/2025/hello-world/"><![CDATA[<p>Hello World!</p> <p>This is my first ever blog post on my brand-new website! I’ve always wanted one, and now I’m absolutely stoked to start off the new year with this first blog post.</p> <p>New years typically start off with resolutions, and here are a few of mine:</p> <p>1) Work harder at LeetCode: This primarily involves expanding my algorithmic toolbox with regards to some of the more complicated data structures around like graphs and trees, while also getting better at Dynamic Programming (because all the interviewers love dynamic programming :stuck_out_tongue_closed_eyes: )</p> <p>2) Sleep on time, wake up on time and work out regularly: This is something I started focusing on in earnest towards the end of 2024, and I want to keep at it through 2025.</p> <p>3) Work on my side projects: get back to my old ones, possibly refactor them entirely (hah!), and flesh them out if I need to</p> <p>2025 is going to be a massive year of change for me, just like 2024 was, and I can’t wait to get stuck in to my next quarter of classes at UCSD (I have some absolute bangers lined up, blog posts on them will be up in due course), as well as my side projects.</p> <p>Wishing everyone who reads this the happiest of new years, Aronya</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="general"/><category term="blog"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first ever blog post on my new website!]]></summary></entry></feed>